Privacy Policy
==============

Your privacy is critically important to us. At _keybr.com_ we have a few fundamental principles:

* We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
* We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
* We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on–going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

Website Visitors
----------------

Like most website operators, _keybr.com_ collects non–personally–identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. _keybr.com_’s purpose in collecting non–personally identifying information is to better understand how _keybr.com_’s visitors use its website. From time to time, _keybr.com_ may release non–personally–identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

_keybr.com_ also collects potentially personally–identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. _keybr.com_ does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally–identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of Personally–Identifying Information
-----------------------------------------------

Certain visitors to _keybr.com_’s websites choose to interact with _keybr.com_ in ways that require _keybr.com_ to gather personally–identifying information. The amount and type of information that _keybr.com_ gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with _keybr.com_ are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, _keybr.com_ collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitors interaction with _keybr.com_. _keybr.com_ does not disclose personally–identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally–identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website–related activities.

Aggregated Statistics
---------------------

_keybr.com_ may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, _keybr.com_ may monitor the most popular pages on this site. _keybr.com_ may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, _keybr.com_ does not disclose personally–identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally–Identifying Information
--------------------------------------------------------

_keybr.com_ discloses personally–identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on _keybr.com_’s behalf or to provide services available at _keybr.com_’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using _keybr.com_’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. _keybr.com_ will not rent or sell potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, _keybr.com_ discloses potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when _keybr.com_ believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of _keybr.com_, third parties or the public at large. _keybr.com_ takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally–identifying and personally–identifying information.

Security of Your Personally–Identifying Information
---------------------------------------------------

When we collect and process personally–identifying information, and while we retain this information, we will protect it within commercially acceptable means to prevent loss and theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification.

Although we will do our best to protect the personal information you provide to us, we advise that no method of electronic transmission or storage is 100% secure, and no one can guarantee absolute data security. We will comply with laws applicable to us in respect of any data breach.

Deleting Your Personally–Identifying Information
------------------------------------------------

We only keep your personally–identifying information as long as you have a user account in _keybr.com_. You can delete your personally–identifying information by deleting an account. To delete your account follow these steps:

1. Sing-in to your existing account.
2. Visit the `Account` page.
3. Click the `Delete Account` button.

Please note that deleting an account is a permanent operation which cannot be undone.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
==============================

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Cookie Declaration
==================

[info@keybr.com](mailto:info@keybr.com "Send your comments and suggestions to info@keybr.com")[Discord](https://discord.gg/gY4RA4enVH "Discuss on our Discord server.")[Github](https://github.com/aradzie/keybr.com "The source code of keybr.com is available on Github.")[Terms of Service](https://www.keybr.com/terms-of-service "Terms of service.")[Privacy Policy](https://www.keybr.com/privacy-policy "Privacy policy.")[English](https://www.keybr.com/privacy-policy)[ar](https://www.keybr.com/ar/privacy-policy "العربية / Arabic") [bg](https://www.keybr.com/bg/privacy-policy "Български / Bulgarian") [ca](https://www.keybr.com/ca/privacy-policy "Català / Catalan") [cs](https://www.keybr.com/cs/privacy-policy "Čeština / Czech") [da](https://www.keybr.com/da/privacy-policy "Dansk / Danish") [de](https://www.keybr.com/de/privacy-policy "Deutsch / German") [el](https://www.keybr.com/el/privacy-policy "Ελληνικά / Greek") [eo](https://www.keybr.com/eo/privacy-policy "Esperanto / Esperanto") [es](https://www.keybr.com/es/privacy-policy "Español / Spanish") [et](https://www.keybr.com/et/privacy-policy "Eesti / Estonian") [fa](https://www.keybr.com/fa/privacy-policy "فارسی / Persian") [fr](https://www.keybr.com/fr/privacy-policy "Français / French") [he](https://www.keybr.com/he/privacy-policy "עברית / Hebrew") [hr](https://www.keybr.com/hr/privacy-policy "Hrvatski / Croatian") [hu](https://www.keybr.com/hu/privacy-policy "Magyar / Hungarian") [id](https://www.keybr.com/id/privacy-policy "Indonesia / Indonesian") [it](https://www.keybr.com/it/privacy-policy "Italiano / Italian") [ja](https://www.keybr.com/ja/privacy-policy "日本語 / Japanese") [ko](https://www.keybr.com/ko/privacy-policy "한국어 / Korean") [ne](https://www.keybr.com/ne/privacy-policy "नेपाली / Nepali") [nl](https://www.keybr.com/nl/privacy-policy "Nederlands / Dutch") [pl](https://www.keybr.com/pl/privacy-policy "Polski / Polish") [pt-br](https://www.keybr.com/pt-br/privacy-policy "Português (Brasil) / Brazilian Portuguese") [pt-pt](https://www.keybr.com/pt-pt/privacy-policy "Português Europeu / European Portuguese") [ro](https://www.keybr.com/ro/privacy-policy "Română / Romanian") [ru](https://www.keybr.com/ru/privacy-policy "Русский / Russian") [sv](https://www.keybr.com/sv/privacy-policy "Svenska / Swedish") [th](https://www.keybr.com/th/privacy-policy "ไทย / Thai") [tr](https://www.keybr.com/tr/privacy-policy "Türkçe / Turkish") [uk](https://www.keybr.com/uk/privacy-policy "Українська / Ukrainian") [vi](https://www.keybr.com/vi/privacy-policy "Tiếng Việt / Vietnamese") [zh-hans](https://www.keybr.com/zh-hans/privacy-policy "简体中文 / Simplified Chinese") [zh-hant](https://www.keybr.com/zh-hant/privacy-policy "繁體中文 / Traditional Chinese")[Translate](https://github.com/aradzie/keybr.com/blob/master/docs/translations.md "Help us translate keybr.com into your language.")[Remove Ads](https://www.keybr.com/account "Purchase a premium account to remove ads.")
